CRAIG PUTZSTUCK

P: 512.317.1374 | E: putzstuck@gmail.com | Port Richey, FL 34668 LINKEDIN | GITHUB | PORTFOLIO

SUMMARY

Accomplished coding bootcamp graduate seeking full stack JavaScript developer roles. Proficient in various coding languages, developing applications and creating MERN projects from the ground up. 5+ years of experience in logistics, scheduling, inventory management and interpersonal communication.

SKILLS			
MongoDB	Third-Party API	HTML5	Bootstrap
MySQL	Express JS	CSS3	Handlebars JS
Mongoose JS	GitHub	React	MVC Paradigm
jQuery	Server-Side API	JavaScript ES6+	Node JS
PROJECTS			

MAGIC: THE GATHERING DECK CREATION

GITHUB URL | DEPLOYED URL

- Summary: Gaming site featuring user accounts and MTG cards.
- Role: Front end developer.
- Tools: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Google Fonts, Photoshop, JavaScript, jQuery, MySQL, Node/Express.js

5-DAY WEATHER FORECAST APP

GITHUB URL | DEPLOYED URL

- Summary: Application providing current and forecasted weather.
- Role: Sole author.
- Tools: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Google Fonts, Client-side Storage, JavaScript, jQuery, Third-party API

EXPERIENCE

WAREHOUSE MANAGER

2020 - 2022

West Shore Home

Tampa, FL

- Predictively manage stock inventory levels and forecast upcoming events to prevent material shortages.
- Precisely receive product deliveries and quickly notify relevant parties of expedited or damaged product.

WAREHOUSE MANAGER

2017 - 2020

Denver Hardwood

Colorado Springs, CO

- Critically review delivery schedules with other departments and the customer to ensure accuracy.
- Accurately controlled inventory through frequent cycle counts and subsequent adjustment.

EDUCATION

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT

2022

University of Central Florida

Remote

IMMERSIVE STUDY ABROAD

2004 - 2005

Universität Lüneburg

Lüneburg, Germany

B.A. IN MATHEMATICS

2003 - 2005

University of Colorado Completed 65 credit hours Colorado Springs, CO